Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photograph files
  - 2-80-065 to 2-80-124, 1980-02 (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - 2-80-125 to 2-80-173, 1980-02 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - 2-80-174 to 2-80-234, 1980-02 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-03 (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - March 1980 Central magazine (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparency, 1980-03 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - 3-80-001 to 3-80-052, 1980-03 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - 3-80-053 to 3-80-109, 1980-03 (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - 3-80-110 to 3-80-175, 1980-03 (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - 3-80-176 to 3-80-226, 1980-03 (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - 3-80-227 to 3-80-276, 1980-03 (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-04 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - April 1980 Central magazine (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparency, and memorandum, 1980-04 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - 4-80-001 to 4-80-057, 1980-04 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - 4-80-058 to 4-80-114, 1980-04 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - 4-80-115 to 4-80-172, 1980-04 (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - 4-80-173 to 4-80-226, 1980-04 (Box 254, Folder 7)
  - 4-80-227 to 4-80-274, 1980-04 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - 4-80-275 to 4-80-334, 1980-04 (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-05 (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - May 1980 Central magazine (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparency, memorandum, and draft of tomato list, 1980-05 (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - 5-80-001 to 5-80-063, 1980-05 (Box 255, Folder 6)
  - 5-80-064 to 5-80-109, 1980-05 (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - 5-80-110 to 5-80-162, 1980-05 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - 5-80-163 to 5-80-221, 1980-05 (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - 5-80-222 to 5-80-266, 1980-05 (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - 5-80-267 to 5-80-324, 1980-05 (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-06 (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - June 1980 Central magazine, 1980-06 (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparency, 1980-06 (Box 256, Folder 7)
  - 6-80-001 to 6-80-057, 1980-06 (Box 256, Folder 8)
  - 6-80-058 to 6-80-110, 1980-06 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - 6-80-111 to 6-80-167, 1980-06 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - 6-80-169 to 6-80-213, 1980-06 (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - 6-80-214 to 6-80-261, 1980-06 (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-07 (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - July 1980 Central magazine (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1980-07 (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - 7-80-001 to 7-80-053, 1980-07 (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - 7-80-054 to 7-80-118, 1980-07 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - 7-80-119 to 7-80-173, 1980-07 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - 7-80-174 to 7-80-221, 1980-07 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - 7-80-222 to 7-80-270, 1980-07 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-08 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - August 1980 Central magazine (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memorandum, 1980-08 (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - 8-80-001 to 8-80-063, 1980-08 (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - 8-80-064 to 8-80-123, 1980-08 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - 8-80-125 to 8-80-178, 1980-08 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - 8-80-179 to 8-80-245, 1980-08 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-09 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - September 1980 Central magazine (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - Slides "Missing Cover", 1980-09 (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - 9-80-002 to 9-80-060, 1980-09 (Box 259, Folder 7)
  - 9-80-062 to 9-80-116, 1980-09 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - 9-80-117 to 9-80-170, 1980-09 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - 9-80-171 to 9-80-219, 1980-09 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - 9-80-220 to 9-80-267, 1980-09 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-10 (Box 260, Folder 5)
  - October 1980 Central magazine (Box 260, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparency, and color photographs, 1980-10 (Box 260, Folder 7)
  - 10-80-001 to 10-80-061, 1980-10 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - 10-80-062 to 10-80-116, 1980-10 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - 10-80-117 to 10-80-183, 1980-10 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - 10-80-184 to 10-80-242, 1980-10 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - 10-80-243 to 10-80-289, 1980-10 (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - 10-80-290 to 10-80-342, 1980-10 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-11 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - 1980 Central magazine (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1980-11 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - 11-80-001 to 11-80-057, 1980-11 (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - 11-80-058 to 11-80-120, 1980-11 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - 11-80-121 to 11-80-173, 1980-11 (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - 11-80-174 to 11-80-212, 1980-11 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - 11-80-214 to 11-80-262, 1980-11 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-12 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - December 1980 Central magazine (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1980-12 (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - 12-80-059 to 12-58-058, 1980-12 (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - 12-80-059 to 12-80-116, 1980-12 (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - 12-80-117 to 12-80-171, 1980-12 (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - 12-80-172 to 12-80-227, 1980-12 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-01 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - January 1981 Central magazine (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1981-01 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - 1-81-002 to 1-81-055, 1981-01 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - 1-81-056 to 1-81-166, 1981-01 (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - 1-81-117 to 1-81-155, 1981-01 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - 1-81-156 to 1-81-196, 1981-01 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-02 (Box 264, Folder 9)
  - February 1981 Central magazine, 1981-02 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Slides, transparency, and memos, 1981-02 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - 2-81-003 to 2-81-050, 1981-02 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - 2-81-051 to 2-81-114, 1981-02 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - 2-81-115 to 2-81-172, 1981-02 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - 2-81-173 to 2-81-220, 1981-02 (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - 2-81-221 to 2-81-278, 1981-02 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-03 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - March 1981 Central magazine (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1981-03 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - 3-81-001 to 3-81-052, 1981-03 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - 3-81-053 to 3-81-120, 1981-03 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - 3-81-121 to 3-81-177, 1981-03 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - 3-81-178 to 3-81-236, 1981-03 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - 3-81-237 to 3-81-296, 1981-03 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-04 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - April 1981 Central magazine (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - April 1981 slides and transparency, 1981-04 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - 4-81-001 to 4-81-048, 1981-04 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - 4-81-051 to 4-81-105, 1981-04 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - 4-81-106 to 4-81-155, 1981-04 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - 4-81-156 to 4-81-208, 1981-04 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - 4-81-209 to 4-81-260, 1981-04 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - 4-81-261 to 4-81-305, 1981-04 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-05 (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - May 1981 Central magazine (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1981-05 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - 5-81-001 to 5-81-057, 1981-05 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - 5-81-058 to 5-81-114, 1981-05 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - 5-81-115 to 5-81-186, 1981-05 (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - 5-81-188 to 5-81-246, 1981-05 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - 5-81-247 to 5-81-288, 1981-05 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - 5-81-289 to 5-81-327, 1981-05 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - 5-81-328 to 5-81-373, 1981-05 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-06 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - June 1981 Central magazine (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - 6-81-001 to 6-81-055, 1981-06 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - 6-81-056 to 6-81-109, 1981-06 (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - 6-81-110 to 6-81-163, 1981-06 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - 6-81-164 to 6-81-212, 1981-06 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - 6-81-213 to 6-81-259, 1981-06 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - 6-81-260 to 6-81-308, 1981-06 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-07 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - July 1981 Central magazine (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparency, 1981-07 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - 7-81-001 to 7-81-058, 1981-07 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - 7-81-059 to 7-81-114, 1981-07 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - 7-81-115 to 7-81-171, 1981-07 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - 7-81-172 to 7-81-210, 1981-07 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - 7-81-211 to 7-81-267, 1981-07 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-08 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - August 1981 Central magazine (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1981-08 (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - 8-81-001 to 8-81-053, 1981-08 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - 8-81-054 to 8-81-114, 1981-08 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - 8-81-118 to 8-81-167, 1981-08 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - 8-81-168 to 8-81-203, 1981-08 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - 8-81-204 to 8-81-241, 1981-08 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-09 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - September 1981 Central magazine (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1981-09 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - 9-81-001 to 9-81-051, 1981-09 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - 9-81-052 to 9-81-107, 1981-09 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - 9-81-108 to 9-81-163, 1981-09 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - 9-81-164 to 9-81-221, 1981-09 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - 9-81-222 to 9-81-263, 1981-09 (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-10 (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - October 1981 Central magazine (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Slides and memo, 1981-10 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - 10-81-001 to 10-81-058, 1981-10 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - 10-81-066 to 10-81-127, 1981-10 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - 10-81-128 to 10-81-182, 1981-10 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - 10-81-183 to 10-81-242, 1981-10 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - 10-81-243 to 10-81-300, 1981-10 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - 10-81-301 to 10-81-353, 1981-10 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - 10-81-354 to 10-81-405, 1981-10 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-11 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - November 1981 Central magazine (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1981-11 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - 11-81-001 to 11-81-057, 1981-11 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - 11-81-058 to 11-81-113, 1981-11 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - 11-81-114 to 11-81-169, 1981-11 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - 11-81-170 to 11-81-226, 1981-11 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - 11-81-227 to 11-81-283, 1981-11 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - 11-81-284 to 11-81-333, 1981-11 (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - 11-81-334 to 11-81-378, 1981-11 (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1981-12 (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - December 1981 Central magazine (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1981-12 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - 12-81-001 to 12-81-048, 1981-12 (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - 12-81-049 to 12-81-110, 1981-12 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - 12-81-111 to 12-81-161, 1981-12 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - 12-81-162 to 12-81-203, 1981-12 (Box 279, Folder 1)
  - 12-81-204 to 12-81-246, 1981-12 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-01 (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - January 1982 Central magazine (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - January 1982 Slides, transparency, and memos, 1982-01 (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - 1-82-001 to 1-82-059, 1982-01 (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - 1-82-060 to 1-82-108, 1982-01 (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - 1-82-109 to 1-82-149, 1982-01 (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - 1-82-150 to 1-82-192, 1982-01 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-02 (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - February 1982 Central magazine (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1982-02 (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - 2-82-001 to 2-82-054, 1982-02 (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - 2-82-055 to 2-82-108, 1982-02 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - 2-82-109 to 2-82-149, 1982-02 (Box 280, Folder 7)
  - 2-82-150 to 2-82-191, 1982-02 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - 2-82-192 to 2-82-234, 1982-02 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - 2-82-235 to 2-82-282, 1982-02 (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-03 (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - March 1982 Central magazine (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparency, 1982-03 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - 3-02-001 to 3-82-062, 1982-03 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - 3-82-063 to 3-82-110, 1982-03 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - 3-82-111 to 3-82-148, 1982-03 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - 3-82-149 to 3-82-198, 1982-03 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - 3-82-199 to 3-82-252, 1982-03 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - 3-82-253 to 3-82-296, 1982-03 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - 3-82-297 to 3-82-329, 1982-03 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-04 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - April 1982 Central magazine (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1982-04 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - 4-82-001 to 4-82-051, 1982-04 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - 482-052 to 4-82-098, 1982-04 (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - 4-82-100 to 4-82-148, 1982-04 (Box 283, Folder 7)
  - 4-82-149 to 4-82-200, 1982-04 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - 4-82-201 to 4-82-250, 1982-04 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - 4-82-251 to 4-82-307, 1982-04 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - 4-82-308 to 4-82-363, 1982-04 (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-05 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - May 1982 Central magazine (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 1982-05 (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - 5-82-001 to 5-82-053, 1982-05 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - 5-82-054 to 5-82-101, 1982-05 (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - 5-82-102 to 5-82-150, 1982-05 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - 5-82-151 to 5-82-199, 1982-05 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - 5-82-200 to 5-82-249, 1982-05 (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - 5-82-251 to 5-82-306, 1982-05 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - 5-82-307 to 5-82-357, 1982-05 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-06 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - June 1982 Central magazine (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparency, 1982-06 (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - 6-82-001 to 6-82-056, 1982-06 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - 6-82-057 to 6-82-104, 1982-06 (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - 6-82-105 to 6-82-150, 1982-06 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - 6-82-153 to 6-82-196, 1982-06 (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - 6-82-197 to 6-82-249, 1982-06 (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - 6-82-250 to 6-82-295, 1982-06 (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-07 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - July 1982 Central magazine (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Slides, and transparency, and memo, 1982-07 (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - 7-82-001 to 7-82-060, 1982-07 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - 7-82-061 to 7-82-147, 1982-07 (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - 7-82-105 to 7-82-147, 1982-07 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - 7-82-150 to 7-82-200, 1982-07 (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - 7-82-201 to 7-82-239, 1982-07 (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - 7-82-240 to 7-82-274, 1982-07 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-08 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - August 1982 Central magazine (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1982-08 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - 8-82-001 to 8-82-051, 1982-08 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - 8-82-055 to 8-82-098, 1982-08 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - 8-82-100 to 8-82-148, 1982-08 (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - 8-82-150 to 8-82-188, 1982-08 (Box 289, Folder 8)
  - 8-82-190 to 8-82-216, 1982-08 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-08 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - September 1982 Central magazine (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Slides and memo, 1982-09 (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - 9-82-001 to 9-82-050, 1982-09 (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - 9-82-051 to 9-82-097, 1982-09 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - 9-82-098 to 9-82-143, 1982-09 (Box 290, Folder 7)
  - 9-82-144 to 9-82-191, 1982-09 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - 9-82-192 to 9-82-246, 1982-09 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - 9-82-247 to 9-82-277, 1982-09 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - 9-82-278 to 9-82-322, 1982-09 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-10 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - October 1982 Central magazine (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - Slides, memo, and transparencies, 1982-10 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - 10-82-001 to 10-82-059, 1982-10 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - 10-82-060 to 10-82-109, 1982-10 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - 10-82-112 to 10-82-170, 1982-10 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - 10-82-171 to 10-82-226, 1982-10 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - 10-82-227 to 10-82-280, 1982-10 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - 10-82-282 to 10-82-318, 1982-10 (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - 10-82-319 to 10-82-355, 1982-10 (Box 293, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-11 (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - November 1982 Central magazine (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1982-11 (Box 293, Folder 5)
  - 11-82-001 to 11-82-061, 1982-11 (Box 293, Folder 6)
  - 11-82-074 to 11-82-130, 1982-11 (Box 293, Folder 7)
  - 11-82-131 to 11-82-169, 1982-11 (Box 293, Folder 8)
  - 11-82-170 to 11-82-215, 1982-11 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - 11-82-216 to 11-82-258, 1982-11 (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - 11-82-259 to 11-82-306, 1982-11 (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - 11-82-307 to 11-82-349, 1982-11 (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1982-12 (Box 294, Folder 5)
  - December 1982 Central magazine (Box 294, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1982-12 (Box 294, Folder 7)
  - 12-82-001 to 12-82-049, 1982-12 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - 12-82-050 to 12-82-104, 1982-12 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - 12-82-105 to 12-82-157, 1982-12 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - 12-82-158 to 12-82-199, 1982-12 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - 12-82-200 to 12-82-257, 1982-12 (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-01 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - January 1983 Central magazine (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparency, 1983-01 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - 1-83-001 to 1-83-037, 1983-01 (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - 1-83-038 to 1-83-077, 1983-01 (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - 1-83-078 to 1-83-119, 1983-01 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - 1-83-120 to 1-83-174, 1983-01 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-02 (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - February 1983 Central magazine (Box 296, Folder 9)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-02 (Box 296, Folder 10)
  - 2-83-001 to 2-83-059, 1983-02 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - 2-83-060 to 2-83-108, 1983-02 (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - 2-83-110 to 2-83-144, 1983-02 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - 2-83-145 to 2-83-184, 1983-02 (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - 2-83-185 to 2-83-240, 1983-02 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-03 (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - March 1983 Central magazine (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-03 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - 3-83-000 to 3-83-040, 1983-03 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - 3-83-041 to 3-83-057, 1983-03 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - 3-83-058 to 3-83-094, 1983-03 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - 3-83-095 to 3-83-134, 1983-03 (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - 3-83-135 to 3-83-178, 1983-03 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - 3-83-179 to 3-83-243, 1983-03 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - 3-83-244 to 3-83-303, 1983-03 (Box 299, Folder 2)
  - 3-83-304 to 3-83-363, 1983-03 (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-04 (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - April 1983 Central magazine (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-04 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - 4-83-001 to 4-83-058, 1983-04 (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - 4-83-059 to 4-83-108, 1983-04 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - 4-83-111 to 4-83-159, 1983-04 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - 4-83-160 to 4-83-207, 1983-04 (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - 4-83-208 to 4-83-263, 1983-04 (Box 300, Folder 4)
  - 4-83-264 to 4-83-340, 1983-04 (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-05 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - May 1983 Central magazine (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-05 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - 5-83-001 to 5-83-053, 1983-05 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - 5-83-054 to 5-83-092, 1983-05 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - 5-83-093 to 5-83-138, 1983-05 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - 5-83-093 to 5-83-180, 1983-05 (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - 5-83-181 to 5-83-227, 1983-05 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - 5-83-228 to 5-83-288, 1983-05 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - 5-83-289 to 5-83-349, 1983-05 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-06 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - June 1983 Central magazine (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-06 (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - 6-83-001 to 6-83-064, 1983-06 (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - 6-83-065 to 6-83-119, 1983-06 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - 6-83-120 to 6-83-176, 1983-06 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - 6-83-177 to 6-83-233, 1983-06 (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - 6-83-234 to 6-83-295, 1983-06 (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-07 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - July 1983 Central magazine (Box 303, Folder 6)
  - Slides, memo, and transparencies, 1983-07 (Box 303, Folder 7)
  - 7-83-001 to 7-83-058, 1983-07 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - 7-83-059 to 7-83-100, 1983-07 (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - 7-83-101 to 7-83-146, 1983-07 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - 7-83-147 to 7-83-192, 1983-07 (Box 304, Folder 4)
  - 7-83-193 to 7-83-241, 1983-07 (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-08 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - August 1983 Central magazine (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-08 (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - 8-83-001 to 8-83-051, 1983-08 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - 8-83-052 to 8-83-097, 1983-08 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - 8-83-101 to 8-83-148, 1983-08 (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - 8-83-149 to 8-83-192, 1983-08 (Box 305, Folder 7)
  - 8-83-193 to 8-83-230, 1983-08 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-09 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - September 1983 Central magazine (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-09 (Box 306, Folder 3)
  - 9-83-001 to 9-83-053, 1983-09 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - 9-83-056 to 9-53-104, 1983-09 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - 9-83-105 to 9-83-161, 1983-09 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - 9-83-162 to 9-83-212, 1983-09 (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - 9-83-213 to 9-83-064, 1983-09 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - 9-83-265 to 9-83-317, 1983-09 (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-10 (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - October 1983 Central magazine (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1983-10 (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - 10-83-001 to 10-83-064, 1983-10 (Box 307, Folder 6)
  - 10-83-66 to 10-83-122, 1983-10 (Box 307, Folder 7)
  - 10-83-123 to 10-83-167, 1983-10 (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - 10-83-168 to 10-83-198, 1983-10 (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - 10-83-199 to 10-83-250, 1983-10 (Box 308, Folder 3)
  - 10-83-253 to 10-83-316, 1983-10 (Box 308, Folder 4)
  - 10-83-317 to 10-83-351, 1983-10 (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - 10-83-352 to 10-83-377, 1983-10 (Box 308, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-11 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - November 1983 Central magazine, 1983-11 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1983-11 (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - 11-83-001 to 11-83-059, 1983-11 (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - 11-83-060 to 11-83-108, 1983-11 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - 11-83-109 to 11-83-157, 1983-11 (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - 11-83-159 to 11-83-205, 1983-11 (Box 309, Folder 7)
  - 11-83-206 to 11-83-258, 1983-11 (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - 11-83-259 to 11-83-292, 1983-11 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - 11-83-294 to 11-83-337, 1983-11 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - 11-83-338 to 11-83-376, 1983-11 (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1983-12 (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - December 1983 Central magazine (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1983-12 (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - 12-83-001 to 12-83-055, 1983-12 (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - 12-83-057 to 12-83-111, 1983-12 (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - 12-83-112 to 12-83-157, 1983-12 (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - 12-83-158 to 12-83-210, 1983-12 (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - 12-83-211 to 12-83-267, 1983-12 (Box 311, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-01 (Box 311, Folder 6)
  - January 1984 Central magazine (Box 311, Folder 7)
  - Slides, memos, transparencies, and notes, 1984-01 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - 1-84-001 to 1-84-058, 1984-01 (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - 1-84-059 to 1-84-104, 1984-01 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - 1-84-105 to 1-84-146, 1984-01 (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - 1-84-147 to 1-84-189, 1984-01 (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-02 (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - February 1984 Central magazine (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Slides, memo, and transparencies, 1984-02 (Box 312, Folder 8)
  - 2-84-001 to 2-84-049, 1984-02 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - 2-84-050 to 2-84-090, 1984-02 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - 2-84-091 to 2-84-131, 1984-02 (Box 313, Folder 3)
  - 2-84-132 to 2-84-176, 1984-02 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - 2-84-177 to 2-84-226, 1984-02 (Box 313, Folder 5)